<resources>
    <string name="premium_more_info_title">Primal Premium</string>
    <string name="premium_more_info_close_button">Close</string>
    <string name="premium_more_info_why_premium_question">Why Get Primal Premium?</string>
    <string name="premium_more_info_why_premium_answer">
            Become a Nostr power user and help shape the future! Open protocols like Nostr give us the opportunity to regain control over our online lives.
            \n\nAt Primal, we don’t rely on advertising. We don’t monetize user data. Our users are our customers. Our sole focus is to make the best possible product for our users. We open source all our work to help the Nostr ecosystem flourish. By signing up for Primal Premium, you are enabling us to continue building for Nostr.
            \n\nBe the change you want to see in the world. If you don’t want to be the product, consider being the customer.
    </string>
    <string name="premium_more_info_faq_first_question">How do I get support?</string>
    <string name="premium_more_info_faq_first_answer">Simply email us at support@primal.net and include your Primal Name in the message. Support requests from Premium users are prioritized and typically handled on the same business day.</string>
    <string name="premium_more_info_faq_second_question">Can I change my Primal Name?</string>
    <string name="premium_more_info_faq_second_answer">Yes! If you wish to change your Primal Name, simply use the “Change your Primal Name” option in the Manage Premium section of any Primal app. Your new name will be functional immediately and your old name will be released and available to other users to register.</string>
    <string name="premium_more_info_faq_third_question">Do I have to use my Primal verified name and lightning address?</string>
    <string name="premium_more_info_faq_third_answer">No. As a Primal Premium user you are able to reserve a Primal Name, but you are not required to use it as your nostr verified address (NIP-05), nor the bitcoin lightning address. Simply set any nostr verified address and/or the bitcoin lightning address you wish to use in your Nostr account profile settings.</string>
    <string name="premium_more_info_faq_fourth_question">Do I own my Primal Name indefinitely?</string>
    <string name="premium_more_info_faq_fourth_answer">You have the right to use your Primal Name for the duration of your Primal Premium subscription. After the subscription expires, there is a grace period of 30 days during which your Primal Name will not be available to others to register. Primal Legend users have non-expiring subscriptions, so they can use their Primal Names indefinitely. Please note that all Primal Names are owned by Primal and rented to users. Primal reserves the right to revoke any name if we determine that the name is trademarked by somebody else, that there is a possible case of impersonation, or for any other case of abuse, as determined by Primal. Please refer to our Terms of Service for details.</string>
    <string name="premium_more_info_faq_fifth_question">Can I buy multiple Primal Names?</string>
    <string name="premium_more_info_faq_fifth_answer">We are working on adding the capability to manage multiple Primal Names. In the meantime, feel free to reach out to us via support@primal.net and we will try to accommodate.</string>
    <string name="premium_more_info_faq_sixth_question">Is my payment information associated with my Nostr account?</string>
    <string name="premium_more_info_faq_sixth_answer">No. Primal Premium can be purchased via an iOS App Store in-app purchase, Google Play in-app purchase, or directly over bitcoin lightning via the Primal web app. Regardless of the method of payment, your payment information is not associated with your Nostr account.</string>
    <string name="premium_more_info_faq_seventh_question">Can I extend my subscription? How does that work?</string>
    <string name="premium_more_info_faq_seventh_answer">Yes, you can extend your subscription using any of the payment methods we support: iOS App Store in-app purchase, Google Play in-app purchase, or directly over bitcoin lightning via the Primal web app. Any payment will extend your subscription by the number of months purchased. For example, if you purchase 3 Months of Primal Premium using the Primal web app, and then subscribe again via your mobile device, your subscription expiry date will be four months in the future, and it will continue to be pushed out with every subsequent monthly payment.</string>
    <string name="premium_more_info_faq_eighth_question">If I buy Primal Premium on my phone, will I have access to it on the web?</string>
    <string name="premium_more_info_faq_eighth_answer">Yes. Your Primal Premium subscription is assigned to your Nostr account. Therefore, regardless of the way you choose to subscribe, your Primal Premium subscription will be available to you in all Primal apps: web, iOS, Android.</string>
    <string name="premium_more_info_faq_ninth_question">How does the Nostr contact list backup feature work?</string>
    <string name="premium_more_info_faq_ninth_answer">Primal creates a backup of 100+ most recent versions of your Nostr follow list. If your follow list gets erased or corrupted by another Nostr app, you will be able to restore it using the Contact List Backup tool in the Nostr Tools section for Primal Premium users.</string>
    <string name="premium_more_info_faq_tenth_question">How does the Nostr account content backup feature work?</string>
    <string name="premium_more_info_faq_tenth_answer">Primal archives the complete history of all your Nostr content. You can rebroadcast any subset of your content to your selected set of relays at any time using the Content Backup tool in the Nostr Tools section for Primal Premium users.</string>
    <string name="premium_more_info_faq_eleventh_question">What other Premium features are coming in the future?</string>
    <string name="premium_more_info_faq_eleventh_answer">We are working on a ton of new and exciting features for Primal Premium. We will announce them as we get closer to releasing them. In the meantime, please feel free to reach out and let us know what you would like to see included in Primal Premium. All suggestions are welcome!</string>
    <string name="premium_more_info_faq_twelfth_question">I’d like to support Primal. Can I do more?</string>
    <string name="premium_more_info_faq_twelfth_answer">At Primal, we don’t rely on advertising. We don’t monetize user data. We open source all our work to help the Nostr ecosystem flourish. If you wish to help us continue doing this work, please see how you can support us. Thank you from the entire Primal Team! 🙏❤️</string>

    <string name="premium_more_info_why_premium">Why Premium</string>
    <string name="premium_more_info_features">Features</string>
    <string name="premium_more_info_faq">FAQ</string>

    <string name="premium_more_info_features_table_header_feature">Feature</string>
    <string name="premium_more_info_features_table_header_free">Free</string>
    <string name="premium_more_info_features_table_header_premium">Premium</string>
    <string name="premium_more_info_features_table_first_row">Apps for Web, iOS, Android</string>
    <string name="premium_more_info_features_table_second_row">Built-in bitcoin lightning wallet</string>
    <string name="premium_more_info_features_table_third_row">Global Nostr text and user search</string>
    <string name="premium_more_info_features_table_fourth_row">Media storage capacity</string>
    <string name="premium_more_info_features_table_fifth_row">Media maximum file size</string>
    <string name="premium_more_info_features_table_sixth_row">Verified Nostr Address</string>
    <string name="premium_more_info_features_table_seventh_row">Custom Lightning Address</string>
    <string name="premium_more_info_features_table_eighth_row">VIP Profile on primal.net</string>
    <string name="premium_more_info_features_table_ninth_row">Advanced Nostr search</string>
    <string name="premium_more_info_features_table_tenth_row">Premium paid relay</string>
    <string name="premium_more_info_features_table_eleventh_row">Nostr contact list backup</string>
    <string name="premium_more_info_features_table_twelfth_row">Nostr account content backup</string>
    <string name="premium_more_info_features_table_thirteenth_row">Much more to come!</string>
</resources>